(Sheldon:)That being said, if you don't get a TARDIS,
you stink and your party stinks.
- Do you have a preference?
- I don't care, get the TARDIS.
(Sheldon:)Yes! This party just became a major rager.
(Raj:)By the way, can I borrow
your bullwhip and fedora?
(Howard:)Yeah, sure, whatever.
(Raj:)I was thinking of dressing up as
Indiana Jones's mocha-skinned love child.
(Raj:)Indian Jones.
- Clever.
- What's wrong with you?
(Leonard:)Nothing.
(Raj:)Howard, I've got a party to plan,
don't make me pull it out of you.
(Howard:)Here it is. Bernadette said you guys are
sick of me talking about my trip to space.
(Howard:)Is that true?
(Howard:)- No.
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)We seem to have different approaches here.
(Sheldon:)I was going for helpful honesty,
I have no idea what you're doing.